philstockworld.com 2018-02-15

# PhilStockWorld.com Privacy Policy | Phil's Stock World

We can be reached via e-mail at: [admin@philstockworld.com](mailto:admin@philstockworld.com). 

This Privacy Policy is applicable to the Members of [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/). Your privacy, and the privacy of all [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) Members, is important to us, and we are committed to protecting the personal information you choose to share with us. 

Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy, based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of all information regarding our members and their activities at PhilStockWorld’s web sites. 

Our data collection and privacy practices are described below. This policy tells you, among other things, what information we may gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information, and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at [admin@philstockworld.com](mailto:admin@philstockworld.com) (or at 201.743.8009) if you have any questions regarding its contents. 

**What information do we gather?**

[PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) may obtain three types of information from its Members: 

1\. registration, subscription, or application data, 

2\. site usage data and,

3\. voluntary survey submissions and postings. 

 Registration, Subscription, or Application Data. The only individually identifiable information that [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) seeks about you is that which you are asked to provide when you register or apply for a subscription. This information includes your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and billing information. Sometimes, [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) Members may be asked to provide additional personal information, such as employer and occupation, educational background, areas of expertise, age range, and other demographic information. 

Site Usage Data. We collect non-identifiable information to measure how our Members use [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/)’s web sites. This information may include statistics about the numbers and timing of unique visits to [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/), repeat visits, and which pages are viewed. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Voluntary Postings. [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) offers several avenues for Members to volunteer statements, opinions, or other information which is then made available to others on [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/)’s web sites. We do not require Members to include personally-identifiable information in these postings. In fact, we generally discourage it. The content of voluntary postings are the sole responsibility of the Members who post them, subject to the applicable Usage Agreement. 

**What do we do with personal information about you?**

Your registration and application data will be closely protected. 

Many of the features on [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) are designed to meet the needs and interests of our Members. To support this personalization, we need to be able to identify your account each time you log in to a [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) web site. 

We may combine your application data and information about your usage of our Site with those of all or a particular group of our members, to prepare aggregated, non-identifiable profiles of our members and their activities on our Site. For example, we may track the number of our members who view certain pages or use certain features. Such information, and other aggregated information we derive from individual members' information, allows us to continue to grow and provide you with timely and useful information through our Site. 

We may provide prospective business partners and other third parties with non-identifiable, aggregated information about [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/)’s web site traffic.  However, this aggregated information about website traffic will not include personally-identifiable information such as registration, subscription, application data or individual page-views. 

[PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) also reserves the right to disclose information as required by law, or to the extent that we believe in good faith that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others' rights or property. 

From time to time, [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) may use highly reputable third-party partners/software for email list management, email distribution and survey research. In such cases, specific types of information may be transferred to these third parties so as to enable them to perform specific functions on our behalf. 

[PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) Members will occasionally receive information on products and services that [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) offers. If you do not wish to receive this information you may "opt out" by sending an email stating such to [admin@philstockworld.com](mailto:admin@philstockworld.com) or following the instructions provided at the bottom of all [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) emails. 

Members' personal information will not be provided to third parties. 

**How does[PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) use "cookies"?**

Using [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) ‘s web sites requires that you accept the use of "cookies," which are small files that our web sites send to your Internet browser for storage on your computer's hard drive. [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) uses cookies to facilitate the login process for you across multiple applications on our sites, to measure traffic on our web sites, and to "personalize" your experience as a Member. When you register or apply for membership, [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) assigns a unique identifier to you, and we place a cookie on your computer which will remind our system of that identifier in other areas of our web sites, or the next time you visit one of our web sites. This cookie allows you to access all of your personalized areas of our web sites without having to log on multiple times. If you reject the cookie, you may still use our site, but you will be limited in some areas of our site. The cookies alone cannot be used to identify you. Instead, your computer is assigned an identifier and that identifier is tracked using the cookie. This identifier is meaningful only within our secure database system and your personalized version of [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/). Some of our business partners use cookies on our site, and we have no access to, control over, or responsibility or liability for these cookies. 

We also use cookies to measure activity on our web sites. Our plans for improvements and updates are based on which areas of our web sites are popular and which are not. Everything we learn from these measurements will be used to enrich your experience on our web sites. [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) does not use cookies for promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with third parties. 

**Can you access information about yourself?**

Yes. At any time after you have registered or applied for a membership, you may personally access, review and/or modify the information in your account profile. Upon your making any changes, any new item of information will replace the corresponding information previously provided. 

What happens to my information if I am no longer a [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) Member? 

Former Members. If for any reason you are no longer a Member, your information will be archived in our system. The content of your voluntary postings, if any, will be retained. 

Applicants. If you apply for membership but do not become a Member, your "application information" will be archived in our system. 

**How is your information protected?**

We use industry-standard encryption methods to transmit [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) application data between your computer and ours across the Internet. We restrict access to any transactional portions of our web sites to computers running web browsers that support the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. To use this protection technology, [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) Members need to have an SSL-capable browser, such as Netscape Navigator 4.5 or higher, Microsoft Internet Explorer 4.5 or higher. These browsers will automatically activate the encryption technology when you log on to one of our web sites. 

Please remember that you play a valuable part in data security as well. Your passwords to access our web sites, which you select when you register, subscribe, or join, should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. After you have finished using one or more of our web sites, you should log off and exit your browser so that no unauthorized persons can use our web sites under your name and account information. Remember that any information you voluntarily disclose on-line in any news or message postings, discussion groups or chat rooms may be collected and used by others without your permission. Furthermore, if you provide any information to parties who operate web sites that are linked to or from one or more of our web sites, different policies may apply to their collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. We encourage you to review these external sites' policies carefully before revealing any sensitive or personal information. 

Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. 

**Restrictions on Access by Children**

Federal law restricts our ability to collect information from children online. For this and other reasons, [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) web sites are open only to persons 18 years of age and over. All Applicants are required to certify that they are 18 years of age or over. If we learn that an Applicant is under age 18, his or her access to [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) will be immediately terminated with no further obligation to [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/), and all identifiable information will be deleted. Misrepresenting age is a violation of our Usage Agreements and will not be tolerated. 

**Submitting Information**

Please remember that voluntary postings submitted through our Submission Forms, along with all voluntary postings submitted through our [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) web sites, are subject to widespread distribution. As set forth in [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) Usage Agreements, Members are solely responsible for the content of their postings and must follow acceptable standards of behavior when posting messages online. Voluntary postings by Members become the property of [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/), and we cannot restrict disclosures of or otherwise guarantee the privacy of any information contained in such postings. 

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE USAGE AGREEMENT. 

PSW Investments, LLC d/b/a [PhilStockWorld.com](http://philstockworld.com/) reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting a revised privacy policy on this web page.
